Even the fish are laughing!
Gone Fishin' is a comedy film directed by Christopher Cain.
Two fishing fanatics get in trouble when their
fishing boat gets stolen while on a trip.
Joe Waters, played by Joe Pesci.
Gus Green, played by Danny Glover.
Rita, played by Rosanna Arquette.
Angie, played by Lynn Whitfield.
Billy 'Catch' Pooler, played by Willie Nelson.
Bubba, played by James R. Greene.
Gone Fishin' is a 1997 American comedy film starring Joe Pesci and
Danny Glover as two bumbling fishing enthusiasts.
Nick Brimble, Rosanna Arquette, Lynn Whitfield, and Willie Nelson co-star.
It is the only collaboration between Glover and Pesci
outside of the Lethal Weapon franchise.
Christopher Cain directed the film.
Abrams and Jill Mazursky wrote the film's script.
The film was released on May 30, 1997.
It was panned by critics and was a box-office bomb, grossing
just $19 million against its $53 million budget.
The film explores themes of sea, boat, fishing, rogue.
The tone is lighthearted.